Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Photographs of Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of individuals, 1973-1995; Series II
  - Beirs, Endee J. (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Bennett, Steven C. (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Berger, Charles (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Berman-Award (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Berry, Joseph K. (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Bertino, Joseph R. (M.D.) (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Bigelow, Rodney (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Billingsley, Donald (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - Binkley, Clark S. (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - Blanshard, Brand (Box 84, Folder 33)
  - Birchette, Mark G. (Box 84, Folder 34)
  - Bishop, Joseph, Jr. (Box 84, Folder 35)
  - Black, Dr. Henry R. (Box 84, Folder 36)
  - Black, John (Box 84, Folder 37)
  - Blake, John (Box 84, Folder 38)
  - Bonnardi, Barbara L. (Box 84, Folder 39)
  - Bork, Robert (Box 84, Folder 40)
  - Bottino, Louise (Box 84, Folder 41)
  - Borst, Kenneth J. (Box 84, Folder 42)
  - Braceland, Francis J. (M.D.) (Box 84, Folder 43)
  - Bradford, Colin (Box 84, Folder 44)
  - Brakefield, Xandra (Box 84, Folder 45)
  - Brandenburg, Judith Berman (Box 84, Folder 46)
  - Brandon, Lisa (Box 84, Folder 47)
  - Brennan, Nancy (Box 84, Folder 48)
  - Brewer, Garry D. (Box 84, Folder 49)
  - Brodsky (Box 84, Folder 50)
  - Brosious, Edward C. (Box 84, Folder 51)
  - Brown, Donald J. (Box 84, Folder 52)
  - Browne, Roy (Box 84, Folder 53)
  - Brownell, Samuel (Box 84, Folder 54)
  - Brownstein, Oscar (Box 84, Folder 55)
  - Brubacher, John S. (Box 85, Folder 56)
  - Brumbaugh, Robert S. (Box 85, Folder 57)
  - Bruall, Nancy (Box 85, Folder 58)
  - Brustein, Robert (Box 85, Folder 59)
  - Buckman, John W. (Box 85, Folder 60)
  - Burnett, Jeff (Box 85, Folder 61)
  - Buxton, Claude (Box 85, Folder 62)
  - Calderon, Hector (Box 85, Folder 63)
  - Calhoun, Robert L. (The Rev.) (Box 85, Folder 64)
  - Canady-Blount, Darzetta (Box 85, Folder 65)
  - Cappeillo, Louis (Box 85, Folder 66)
  - Carson, Kimberly (Box 85, Folder 67)
  - Carter, Donald (Box 85, Folder 68)
  - Chaet, Leah (Box 85, Folder 69)
  - Chari, Ravi V.J. (Box 85, Folder 70)
  - Chavez-Brumell, Maria Martha (Box 85, Folder 71)
  - Cherry, Lynne (Box 85, Folder 72)
  - Chein, Ann (Box 85, Folder 73)
  - Chilton, Bruce (Prof.) (Box 85, Folder 74)
  - Chrisman, Bruce L. (Box 85, Folder 75)
  - Cingo, Ms. Nombulelo (South African Nurse) (Box 85, Folder 76)
  - Cizewski, Jolie A. (Box 85, Folder 77)
  - Clark, Ben (Box 85, Folder 78)
  - Clausing, Stephen (Box 85, Folder 79)
  - Caplan, Margi (Box 85, Folder 80)
  - Clement, Margaret Bush (Box 85, Folder 81)
  - Clement, David H. (M.D.) (Box 86, Folder 82)
  - Clouet, Herbert (Box 86, Folder 83)
  - Clouet, Roberta (Box 86, Folder 84)
  - Codish, Kay (Box 86, Folder 85)
  - Coleman, Jules V. (M.D.) (Box 86, Folder 86)
  - Collimore, Jacqueline (Box 86, Folder 87)
  - Connelly, Bernardine '86 (Box 86, Folder 88)
  - Contreras, Robert (Box 86, Folder 89)
  - Cook, John W. (Box 86, Folder 90)
  - Cooke, Michael G. (Box 86, Folder 91)
  - Cormack, Malcolm (Box 86, Folder 92)
  - Couch, A. Edward (Box 86, Folder 93)
  - Cover, Robert (Box 86, Folder 94)
  - Cowgill, Warrren C. (Box 86, Folder 95)
  - Cronon, William J. (Box 86, Folder 96)
  - Crosby, Faye (Box 86, Folder 97)
  - Crosby, Sumner McK. (Box 86, Folder 98)
  - Curran, Mark (Box 86, Folder 99)
  - Curtain, Phyllis (Box 86, Folder 100)
  - Curtis, C. Marvin (Box 86, Folder 101)
  - Daly, Kathleen (Box 86, Folder 102)
  - D'amico, Michael (M.D.) (Box 86, Folder 103)
  - Dauer, Edwards A. (Box 86, Folder 104)
  - Davie, James S. (Box 86, Folder 105)
  - Davis, Doris (Box 86, Folder 106)
  - Davis, Kenneth P. (Box 86, Folder 107)
  - DeCherney, Dr. Alan H. (Box 86, Folder 108)
  - DeLeon, Nelson (Box 86, Folder 109)
  - DeLorenzo, Robert & Lorisa (Box 86, Folder 110)
  - DeMars, Louise Lauretano (Box 87, Folder 111)
  - Demetz, Hana (Box 87, Folder 112)
  - Denison, George A. (Box 87, Folder 113)
  - Dihoff, Ivan (Box 87, Folder 114)
  - Donaldson, Robert (Box 87, Folder 115)
  - Donaldson, William (Box 87, Folder 116)
  - Dorn, Susan (Box 87, Folder 117)
  - Downs, Wilbur G. (M.D.) (Box 87, Folder 118)
  - Dreyfuss, Dale M. (Box 87, Folder 119)
  - DuBois, Margaret (Box 87, Folder 120)
  - Duff, Raymond (M.D.) (Box 87, Folder 121)
  - Dunn, Edward W. Y., Jr. (Box 87, Folder 122)
  - Dwyer, Athena D. (Box 87, Folder 123)
  - Early, Michael (Box 87, Folder 124)
  - Eaton, Richard (Box 87, Folder 125)
  - Edwards, Thomas K. (Box 87, Folder 126)
  - Embersits, John F. (Box 87, Folder 127)
  - Emerson, Thomas I. (Box 87, Folder 128)
  - Engley, Donald B. (Box 87, Folder 129)
  - English, James (Box 87, Folder 130)
  - Estabrook, Henry (Box 87, Folder 131)
  - Estes, Ellen G. (Box 87, Folder 132)
  - Evans, Theodore S. (M.D.) (Box 87, Folder 133)
  - Falk, Isidore Sydney (Box 88, Folder 134)
  - Farnham, Charles S. (Box 88, Folder 135)
  - Farquhar, Marilyn (Box 88, Folder 136)
  - Felig, Philip (M.D.) (Box 88, Folder 137)
  - Fellner, William J. (Box 88, Folder 138)
  - Ferguson, Margaret W. (Box 88, Folder 139)
  - Ferrari, Giovanni (Box 88, Folder 140)
  - Ferris, Gill (Box 88, Folder 141)
  - Fiadeiro, Manuel E. (Box 88, Folder 142)
  - Findlay, John N. (Box 88, Folder 143)
  - Fishkin, James S. (Box 88, Folder 144)
  - Fitch, Frederic B. (Box 88, Folder 145)
  - Flores, Hector (Box 88, Folder 146)
  - Forbes, Thomas R. (Box 88, Folder 147)
  - Foster, Charles (Box 88, Folder 148)
  - Foster, Jacqueline (Box 88, Folder 149)
  - Frank, Meryl (Box 88, Folder 150)
  - Frankfurt, Harry (Box 88, Folder 151)
  - Freeman, Greydon C. (Box 88, Folder 152)
  - Frei, Hans & Geraldine (Box 88, Folder 153)
  - Friday, Sandra (Box 88, Folder 154)
  - Frith, Chester (Box 88, Folder 155)
  - Frohardt, Mark (Box 88, Folder 156)
  - Froula, Christine (Box 88, Folder 157)
  - Fuller, Dollie B. (Box 88, Folder 158)
  - Fuoss, Raymond M.. (Box 88, Folder 159)
  - Gabinellli, Cheryl (Box 88, Folder 160)
  - Gabriel, Ralph H. (Box 89, Folder 161)
  - Gage, Charles (Box 89, Folder 162)
  - Gagge, A. Pharo (Box 89, Folder 163)
  - Gardella, Andy (Box 89, Folder 164)
  - Gambrill, Bessie Lee (Box 89, Folder 165)
  - Gardner, William U. (Box 89, Folder 166)
  - Garibaldi, Gary (Box 89, Folder 167)
  - Gariepy, Thomas (Box 89, Folder 168)
  - Garner, Richard K. (Box 89, Folder 179)
  - Garratt, George A. (Dean) (Box 89, Folder 170)
  - Gates, Henry Louis (Box 89, Folder 171)
  - Gatzke, Hans Wilhelm (Box 89, Folder 172)
  - Gaudon, Jean (Box 89, Folder 173)
  - Gertner, Joseph M.(M.D.) (Box 89, Folder 174)
  - Getman, Julius G. (Box 89, Folder 175)
  - Giamatti, A. B. (Box 89, Folder 176-179)
  - Giamatti, A. B. (see also Oversize) (Box 90, Folder 180-185)
  - Giamatti, A. B. (Box 91, Folder 186-190)
  - Giamatti, A. B. (Box 92, Folder 191-196)
  - Gibbs, Lawrence M. (Box 92, Folder 197)
  - Gibson, Ann (Box 92, Folder 198)
  - Gilmore, Grant (Box 92, Folder 199)
  - Ginnetti, John, Jr. (Box 92, Folder 200)
  - Goldsmith, Raymond (Box 92, Folder 201)
  - Gomez, Jesus (Box 92, Folder 202)
  - Goodkin, Richard (Box 92, Folder 203)
  - Goodyer, Allan V.N. (M.D.) (Box 92, Folder 204)
  - Gottschalk, Alexander (M.D.) (Box 92, Folder 205)
  - Granger, Donald P. (Box 92, Folder 206)
  - Greengard, Paul (Box 92, Folder 207)
  - Griffin, Martin I.J., Jr. (Box 92, Folder 208)
  - Guida, Fred (Box 93, Folder 209)
  - Gursey, Feza (Box 93, Folder 210)
  - Gurthrie, Joseph (Box 93, Folder 211)
  - Haight, Charles J. (Box 93, Folder 212)
  - Halpert, Jim '85 (Box 93, Folder 213)
  - Haight, Gordon S. (Box 93, Folder 214)
  - Hampton, Timothy (Box 93, Folder 215)
  - Handel, Steve (Box 93, Folder 216)
  - Hanna, Archibald (Box 93, Folder 217)
  - Hardin, John A. (M.D.) (Box 93, Folder 218)
  - Hardy, James D. (Box 93, Folder 219)
  - Harvey, Henry (Box 93, Folder 220)
  - Harwood, Caroline S. (Box 93, Folder 221)
  - Hathaway, John S. (M.D.) (Box 93, Folder 222)
  - Havelock, Eric A. (Box 93, Folder 223)
  - Hawrot, Edward (Box 93, Folder 224)
  - Healy, Kent (Box 93, Folder 225)
  - Hedlund, Gustav A. (Box 93, Folder 226)
  - Hedlund, Nancy (Box 93, Folder 227)
  - Hee, Carol (Box 93, Folder 228)
  - Helgerson, Dr. Steven D. (Box 93, Folder 229)
  - Henning, Basil C. (Box 93, Folder 230)
  - Henson, David B. (Box 93, Folder 231)
  - Herbert, Robert L. (Box 93, Folder 232)
  - Herek, Gregory M. (Box 93, Folder 233)
  - Herken, Gregg (Box 93, Folder 234)
  - Herold, Wolf-Dietrich (Box 94, Folder 235)
  - Hersey, John '36 (Box 94, Folder 236)
  - Hess, Orvan W. (M.D.) (Box 94, Folder 237)
  - Hill, Craig (Box 94, Folder 238)
  - Hird, Virginia (Box 94, Folder 239)
  - Hirshfield, Jay L. (Box 94, Folder 240)
  - Hiscock, Ira V. (Box 94, Folder 241)
  - Hobbins, John (Box 94, Folder 242)
  - Holcomb, Wade (Box 94, Folder 243)
  - Holme, Thomas T. (Box 94, Folder 244)
  - Hopkins, Sylvester (Box 94, Folder 245)
  - Hosmer, Debra (Box 94, Folder 246)
  - Howard-Flanders, Paul (M.D.) (Box 94, Folder 247)
  - Hutchinson, G. Evelyn (Box 94, Folder 248)
  - Hyde, Thomas (Box 94, Folder 249)
  - Iannnuzzi, Patricia (Box 94, Folder 250)
  - Ingber, Richard (Box 94, Folder 251)
  - Ingholt, Harald (Box 94, Folder 252)
  - Irvin, Carolyn (Box 94, Folder 253)
  - Isack, Arthur G. (Box 94, Folder 254)
  - Jackson, Caroline (Box 94, Folder 255)
  - Jacoby, Alberta P. (Box 94, Folder 256)
  - Jakovenko, Nadya (Box 94, Folder 257)
  - Jamner, Larry (Box 94, Folder 258)
  - Janis, Irving L. (Box 94, Folder 259)
  - Jervis, Jane (Box 94, Folder 260)
  - Johnson, (Tony) Anthony (Box 95, Folder 261)
  - Johnson, Gladys (Box 95, Folder 262)
  - Johnson, Lester (Box 95, Folder 263)
  - Jones, Ralph C. (Box 95, Folder 264)
  - Jones, Susan (Box 95, Folder 265)
  - Joplin, Patricia (Box 95, Folder 266)
  - Jordan, Richard (Box 95, Folder 267)
  - Josephson, Trina (Box 95, Folder 268)
  - Kanter, Rosabeth Moss (Box 95, Folder 269)
  - Katz, Bradley A. (Box 95, Folder 270)
  - Kauffmann, Stanley (Box 95, Folder 271)
  - Keller, Deane (Box 95, Folder 272)
  - Kenefick, James G. (Box 95, Folder 273)
  - Kessler, Friedrich (Box 95, Folder 274)
  - Kiang, Lindsey C.Y. (Box 95, Folder 275)
  - Kimball, Bruce A. (Box 95, Folder 276)
  - Kipfer, Barbara (Box 95, Folder 277)
  - Kirkpatrick, Ralph (Box 95, Folder 278)
  - Klatskin,Ethelyn H. (Box 95, Folder 279)
  - Klatskin, Gerald (M.D.) (Box 95, Folder 280)
  - Klaus, Sidney N. (M.D.) (Box 95, Folder 281)
  - Kleber, Herbert D. (M.D.) (Box 95, Folder 282)
  - Knowlton, Nancy (Box 95, Folder 283)
  - Koditschek, Daniel E. (Box 95, Folder 284)
  - Koopmans, Tjalling C. (Box 95, Folder 285)
  - Kozarich, John W. (Box 95, Folder 286)
  - Kraemer, Deborah Tebes (Box 95, Folder 287)
  - Krauss, Lawrence M. (Box 95, Folder 288)
  - Krevolin, Richard W. (Box 95, Folder 289)
  - Krishnan, Mahadevan (Box 95, Folder 290)
  - Kubovy, Miri (Box 95, Folder 291)
  - Laeuchli, Ann (Box 95, Folder 292)
  - Lamar, H. (Box 96, Folder 293)
  - Lampo, Guy J. (Box 96, Folder 294)
  - Lande, Saul (Box 96, Folder 295)
  - Lang, Dr. Robert (Box 96, Folder 296)
  - Lansberg, Ivan (Box 96, Folder 297)
  - Larson, Daniel (Box 96, Folder 298)
  - Lawerence, Dr. William (Box 96, Folder 299)
  - LeBeauf, Sabrina (Box 96, Folder 300)
  - Lee, Jack (Box 96, Folder 301)
  - Leff, Arthur A. (Box 96, Folder 302)
  - Lehr, Robert (Box 96, Folder 303)
  - Leonhard, Wolfgang (Box 96, Folder 304)
  - Levine, Hillel (Box 96, Folder 305)
  - Levine, Michael (Box 96, Folder 306)
  - Lewin, Prof. Frank (Box 96, Folder 307)
  - Lewis, Helen Block (Box 96, Folder 308)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S. (Box 96, Folder 309)
  - Liberles, Robert (Box 96, Folder 310)
  - Lifton, Robert J. (M.D.) (Box 96, Folder 311)
  - Lipin, Diane (Box 96, Folder 312)
  - Lippard, Vernon W. (M.D.) (Box 96, Folder 313)
  - Lipsky,Seymour R. (M.D.) (Box 96, Folder 314)
  - Littel, Walter D. (Box 96, Folder 315)
  - Liu, Alan (Box 96, Folder 316)
  - Livstone, Elliot (M.D.) (Box 96, Folder 317)
  - Lopez, Robert (Box 96, Folder 318)
  - Lovett, Rev. Sidney (Box 96, Folder 319)
  - Lowe, Jim (Box 96, Folder 320)
  - Lowell, Gerald R. (Box 96, Folder 321)
  - Lowman, Robert M. (M.D.) (Box 96, Folder 322)
  - Lutz, Harold J. (Box 96, Folder 323)
  - Lyons, William P. (Box 97, Folder 324)
  - MacInerny, Marjorie (Box 97, Folder 325)
  - Mac Mullan, Ramsay (Box 97, Folder 326)
  - MacIntyre, Angus J. (Box 97, Folder 327)
  - McGuire, Edward J. (M.D.) (Box 97, Folder 328)
  - Mclennan, Gloria (Box 97, Folder 329)
  - McMullan, Frank A. (Box 97, Folder 330)
  - McMullan, Snadra Herson (Box 97, Folder 331)
  - Malkiel, Burton G. (Box 97, Folder 332)
  - Manaro, James V. (Box 97, Folder 333)
  - Manuelidis, Elias E. (M.D.) (Box 97, Folder 334)
  - Markert, Clement L. (Box 97, Folder 335)
  - Marston, Thomas E. (Box 97, Folder 336)
  - Martindell, E. Jane (Box 97, Folder 337)
  - Matter, Herbert (Box 97, Folder 338)
  - McCrillis, John O.C. (Box 97, Folder 339)
  - Matzke, Martha K. (Box 97, Folder 340)
  - Menta, John (Box 97, Folder 341)
  - Mergen, Francois (Box 97, Folder 342)
  - Merriman, Daniel (Box 97, Folder 343)
  - Mesquitta, Joseph (Box 97, Folder 344)
  - Meusel, Harry W. (Box 97, Folder 345)
  - Mick, Stephen (Box 97, Folder 346)
  - Migdalski, Edward C. (Box 97, Folder 347)
  - Milgrom, Paul R. (Box 97, Folder 348)
  - Miller, J. Hillis (Box 97, Folder 349)
  - Miller, Richard S. (Box 97, Folder 350)
  - Miluso, Leo (Box 98, Folder 351)
  - Mitchell, Alphonsus (Box 98, Folder 352)
  - Mitchell, Juliet (Box 98, Folder 353)
  - Morhlman, PatriciaMoore (Box 98, Folder 354)
  - Moore, Charles W. (Box 98, Folder 355)
  - Moore, Leslie (Box 98, Folder 356)
  - Moriarty, Philip E. (Box 98, Folder 357)
  - Morowitz, Harold (Box 98, Folder 358)
  - Morris, John McL. (M.D.) (Box 98, Folder 359)
  - Morris, Raymond P. (Box 98, Folder 360)
  - Morris, Sarah (Box 98, Folder 361)
  - Mueller, Georgette (Box 98, Folder 362)
  - Muhlfeldt, John (Box 98, Folder 363)
  - Mullen, Edwin (Box 98, Folder 364)
  - Murphy, David G. (Box 98, Folder 365)
  - Murphy, Maureen M. (Box 98, Folder 366)
  - Mylong, Ernst (M.D.) (Box 98, Folder 367)
  - Nagler, Alois M. (Box 98, Folder 368)
  - Naylor, Gloria (Box 98, Folder 369)
  - Needham, Wesley E. (Box 98, Folder 370)
  - Nelson, Philip (Box 98, Folder 371)
  - Nelson, Richard (Box 98, Folder 372)
  - Neville, Tom (Box 98, Folder 373)
  - Ngugi, Mr. Wa Thioong'o (Box 98, Folder 374)
  - Nichols, Carol Wood (Box 98, Folder 375)
  - Noble, Lawrence (Box 98, Folder 376)
  - Nochlin, Linda (Box 98, Folder 377)
  - Nolan, William J. (Box 98, Folder 378)
  - Northrop, Filmer S.C. (Box 98, Folder 379)
  - Noyes, Edward M. (Box 99, Folder 380)
  - Odendahl, Teresa (Box 99, Folder 381)
  - Ohr, William L. (Box 99, Folder 382)
  - Okpaku, Dr. Samuel (Box 99, Folder 383)
  - Olsen, Michael (Box 99, Folder 384)
  - Olyan, Saul (Box 99, Folder 385)
  - Onofrio, John W., Jr. (Box 99, Folder 386)
  - Osgood, Cornelius (Box 99, Folder 387)
  - Osterweis, Rollin G. (Box 99, Folder 388)
  - Owen, Benton B. (Box 99, Folder 389)
  - Ozawa, Kaz (Box 99, Folder 390)
  - Pagnelli, Robert P. (Box 99, Folder 391)
  - Paladino, Greg (Box 99, Folder 392)
  - Parish, Howard F. (Box 99, Folder 393)
  - Patrick, Hugh (Box 99, Folder 394)
  - Patterson, Andrew, Jr. (Box 99, Folder 395)
  - Paulson, Ronald H. (Box 99, Folder 396)
  - Pearson, David A. (Box 99, Folder 397)
  - Peckham, Mary (Box 99, Folder 398)
  - Peixoto, Prof. Marta (Box 99, Folder 399)
  - Penney, Sherry H. (Box 99, Folder 400)
  - Perlis, Alan J. (Box 99, Folder 401)
  - Peters, William (Box 99, Folder 402)
  - Peterson, Stephen L. (Box 99, Folder 403)
  - Peyre, Henri (Box 99, Folder 404)
  - Phillips, Aris (Box 99, Folder 405)
  - Phillips, William C. (Box 99, Folder 406)
  - Pickford, Grace (Box 99, Folder 407)
  - Piekos, Millie (Box 99, Folder 408)
  - Pierson, George (Box 99, Folder 409)
  - Pilbeam, David (Box 99, Folder 410)
  - Pincus, Jonathan H. (M.D.) (Box 100, Folder 411)
  - Platt, Terry (M.D.) (Box 100, Folder 412)
  - Plotke, David (Box 100, Folder 413)
  - Polan, Dr. Mary Lake (Box 100, Folder 414)
  - Poling, Wesley H. (Box 100, Folder 415)
  - Pottles, Frederick and Marian (Box 100, Folder 416)
  - Poulson, Donald F. (Box 100, Folder 417)
  - Poznansky, Alexander (Box 100, Folder 418)
  - Price, Derek de Solla (Box 100, Folder 419)
  - Provasolli, Luigi (Box 100, Folder 420)
  - Provence, Sally A. (M.D.) (Box 100, Folder 421)
  - Quilligan, Maureen (Box 100, Folder 422)
  - Rahder, Johannes (Box 100, Folder 423)
  - Ramsbottam, Mary (Box 100, Folder 424)
  - Rannit, Alexis (Box 100, Folder 425)
  - Rasmussen, Howard (M.D.) (Box 100, Folder 426)
  - Redlich, Fredrick C. (Box 100, Folder 427)
  - Reed, Adolph L. Jr. (Box 100, Folder 428)
  - Reichardt, Antoinette (Box 100, Folder 429)
  - Rentzepis, Peter (Box 100, Folder 430)
  - Rhoads, Donald C. (Box 100, Folder 431)
  - Robinson, Abraham (Box 100, Folder 432)
  - Robinson, Charles Emitt (Box 100, Folder 433)
  - Robley, Grant (Box 100, Folder 434)
  - Rodriguez, Bill (Box 100, Folder 435)
  - Romero, Mary (Box 100, Folder 436)
  - Rosenberg, Leon (M.D.) (Box 100, Folder 437)
  - Rosenberg, Mindy (Box 100, Folder 438)
  - Rosenstone, Steven J. (Box 100, Folder 439)
  - Rossomando, Joseph (Box 100, Folder 440)
  - Rothenberg, Albert (M.D.) (Box 100, Folder 441)
  - Royster, Eunice (Box 100, Folder 442)
  - Rush, James R. (Box 101, Folder 443)
  - Rudney, Gabriel (Box 101, Folder 444)
  - Russell, Richard R. (The Rev.) (Box 101, Folder 445)
  - Rutenberg, Laurie (Box 101, Folder 446)
  - Ryan, Frank (Box 101, Folder 447)
  - Ryerson, Ellen (Box 101, Folder 448)
  - Sachs, Louis (Box 101, Folder 449)
  - Sah, Raaj K. (Box 101, Folder 450)
  - Samuel, Arthur G. (Box 101, Folder 451)
  - Sass, Austin (Box 101, Folder 452)
  - Schank, Roger (Box 101, Folder 453)
  - Schmidt, B.C. (Box 101, Folder 454-458)
  - Schmidt, B.C. (Box 102, Folder 459-465)
  - Schmidt, B.C (Box 103, Folder 466-471)
  - Schreiber, Stuart (Box 103, Folder 472)
  - Schultz, T. Paul (Box 103, Folder 473)
  - Schwartz, Eve (Box 103, Folder 474)
  - Schwartz, Gary E. (Box 103, Folder 475)
  - Scott, Dennis (Box 103, Folder 476)
  - Screenivasan, Katepali (Box 103, Folder 477)
  - Sears, Paul B. (Box 103, Folder 478)
  - Selesky, Harold E. (Box 103, Folder 479)
  - Senn, Milton J.E. (M.D.) (Box 103, Folder 480)
  - Serene, Joseph (Box 103, Folder 481)
  - Sereni, Maria (Box 103, Folder 482)
  - Sewall, Margaret (Box 103, Folder 483)
  - Shanley, Mark S. (Box 103, Folder 484)
  - Shepard, Brooks J.R. (Box 103, Folder 485)
  - Shestack, Alan (Box 103, Folder 486)
  - Shimada, Nadine (Box 103, Folder 487)
  - Shumway, Nicolas (Box 103, Folder 488)
  - Siggins, Jack (Box 103, Folder 489)
  - Similon, Philippe L. (Box 103, Folder 490)
  - Simonds, Bruce (Box 103, Folder 491)
  - Simone, Debra (Box 103, Folder 492)
  - Simpson, Patricia (Box 103, Folder 493)
  - Smith, Ora K. (Box 104, Folder 494)
  - Snoke, Albert W. (M.D.) (Box 104, Folder 495)
  - Snyder, Joseph C. (Box 104, Folder 496)
  - Soulliere, Anne-Marie (Box 104, Folder 497)
  - Spadafora, David (Box 104, Folder 498)
  - Spacks, Patricia (Box 104, Folder 499)
  - Spates, Thomas G. (Box 104, Folder 500)
  - Specht, Robert (Box 104, Folder 501)
  - Stacey, Robin Chapman (Box 104, Folder 502)
  - Stacey, Robert C. (Box 104, Folder 503)
  - Stanfield, John H. II (Box 104, Folder 504)
  - Steere, Allen C. Jr. (Box 104, Folder 505)
  - Stein, Josh (Box 104, Folder 506)
  - Steinberg, Susan J. (Box 104, Folder 507)
  - Stepan, Alfred (Box 104, Folder 508)
  - Stern, Blake G. (Box 104, Folder 509)
  - Stevens, Charles (Box 104, Folder 510)
  - Stevens, Jerald L. (Box 104, Folder 511)
  - Stoddard, Carlos F, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 512)
  - Storrs, David K. (Box 104, Folder 513)
  - Stritzel, Ursala (Box 104, Folder 514)
  - Sullivan, Maureen (Box 104, Folder 515)
  - Sussex, Ian M. (Box 104, Folder 516)
  - Taft, Horace D. (Box 104, Folder 517)
  - Tally, Sandra (Box 104, Folder 518)
  - Taylor, Charles H. Jr. (Box 104, Folder 519)
  - Taylor, Elise (Box 104, Folder 520)
  - Tennant, Mary E. (Box 104, Folder 521)
  - Thalman, William G. (Box 104, Folder 522)
  - Thier, Samuel O. (M.D.) (Box 104, Folder 523)
  - Thompson, John D. (Box 104, Folder 524)
  - Thomson, Keith S. (Box 105, Folder 525)
  - Thouless, David J. (Box 105, Folder 526)
  - Tiffney, Bruce H. (Box 105, Folder 527)
  - Tinsley, Beatrice (Box 105, Folder 528)
  - Tippo, Denis R. (Box 105, Folder 529)
  - Tischler, Gary L. (Box 105, Folder 530)
  - Torre, Carlos A. (Box 105, Folder 531)
  - Tracy, Robert J. (Box 105, Folder 532)
  - Treder, Frederick H.(M.D.) (Box 105, Folder 533)
  - Triffin, Robert (Box 105, Folder 534)
  - Turnamian, Steven (M.D.) (Box 105, Folder 535)
  - Tuteur, Franz B. (Box 105, Folder 536)
  - Tweed, Ellen (Box 105, Folder 537)
  - Underwood, Barbara (Box 105, Folder 538)
  - Vaill, George D. (Box 105, Folder 539)
  - Van Den Dorpal, Ronald (Box 105, Folder 540)
  - Vannorsdall, John (The Rev) (Box 105, Folder 541)
  - Vigilante, Kevin (M.D.) (Box 105, Folder 542)
  - Villarreal, Edit (Box 105, Folder 543)
  - Viseltear, Arthur J. (Box 105, Folder 544)
  - Von Schlegell, David (Box 105, Folder 545)
  - Wahba, Grace (Box 105, Folder 546)
  - Waite, Patricia J. (Box 105, Folder 547)
  - Wakeman, Edward T. (M.D.) (Box 105, Folder 548)
  - Wald, Florence Schorske (Box 105, Folder 549)
  - Ward, Barbara & Gerald (Box 105, Folder 550)
  - Warnke, Georgia (Box 105, Folder 551)
  - Warren, Robert Penn (Box 105, Folder 552)
- Oversize, 1978; Series III
  - Giamatti, A. Bartlett, inauguration, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 553)
- Photographs of Yale Administrators, Faculty and Alumni, circa 1980s-1990s; Accession 2010-A-049
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - Photographs of Yale administrators, faculty and alumni, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 1)
- Photographs of Yale Faculty, Circa 1966-2005; Accession 2011-A-025
  - Aaboe, Asger, 1966, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abell, Millicent, 1977, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abelson, Robert F., 1982, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ablow, Ronald, C., M.D., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ackerman, Janet H., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Adair, Eleanor, 1988, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adair, Robert K., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adams, Rev. Hary B., 1988, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adams, Robert, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adelberg, Edward A., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adorno, Rolena, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aghajanian, George, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Ague, Jay, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Aki, Syoko, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alderman, Nigel, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alexander, Bruce, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Allen, Greer, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Allison, Truett, 1988, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Altman, Sidney, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Altman, Sidney, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Amanat, Abbas, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ameling, Ann T., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Anderson, Christy, 1996, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Anderson, David G., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Anderson, Michael, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Andrews, Steven, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Annand, Rev. James, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Anscombe, Francis, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Antle, Rick, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Apfel, Robert E., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Appadurai, Arjun, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Appelquist, Thomas, 1977-1997 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Aptner, David, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Armor, David, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Armstrong, Judith, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Arnold, Thomas, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Arnstein, Robert, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Aronson, Peter S., M.D, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Arthaud, Greg, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Atkins, Elisha, M.D., 1978, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 40)